「発」…　「練」で増大させた 念オーラを最終的に発する技
This is a bullet casing.
もちろん　「ダブル」は ただの　まやかしではなく
who ruled this country from the shadows.
それは　「ダブル」の攻撃を受けて 実感しただろ？
It's safe to assume that the Chimera Ants
つまり　お前は　２人の私を 相手にしなければならない。
have assumed control of NGL's interior. The question is if we can reach their nest
これが　「念」によって完成した 真の「虎咬拳」。
before the Queen births the King.
それにより右腕を失った ヒソカ
More!
果たして 両者の勝負の行方は…
More! I need much more.
ウフ。
I need more food of high
nutritional value for my child.
おやおや？　ヒソカ選手が スカーフで右腕を覆い隠した！
Yes, the Queen has requested more food, to aid the King's growth.
僕の予知能力を　お見せしようか。
We've been providing fifty a day.
おっと！ なんと右腕が消えて
to assemble enough soldiers to ease the job...
トランプが宙に舞う！ 一体　何をする気だ!?
If the Queen commands, we will double or triple our quota. We should increase our ranks...
まず　この中から好きな数を選んで 頭に思い浮かべて。
We must start by instilling more discipline. We'll increase our ranks afterwards. First, we must eliminate sedition in all—
好きな数字？
Don't make me laugh!
その数に４を足して さらに倍にする。
The rare human I captured has the
nutritional value of a thousand normal ones.
そこから６を引き ２で割った後
One with the value of a thousand? What are you talking about?
最初に頭に思い浮かべた数を 引くと　いくつになる？ えっと…。 ねぇ！　６を引くんだっけ？
You didn't know? I'm saying that some unique humans
are overflowing with life energy.
あ　もう　分かんない！ 僕には　その答えが あらかじめ分かっていた。
They're hard to find, which is why they're rare. Rare?
キャ！ うわ！
These special humans each have the
nutritional value of a thousand normal ones? That's right.
その数字は　１だ。
I saw and fought one.
当たった！ 何で？
And then, I accidentally took a bite!
マジ!?
Pike!
異常です！ まさに狂気！　悪魔の手品です！
The one you took a bite out of wasn't rare.
自分の傷口に ネタを仕込んでいました！
Oh, yeah. You're right. Don't spout nonsense!
何なんだ？ あいつの　あの余裕は…
Your words were also nonsense, Zazan-sama. I spoke nonsense? When?
ポイントにもならない 試合にも　一切関係なし！
You weren't the one who
captured the rare human.
…にもかかわらずです！
I did.
ヒソカ選手の異常性 ここに極まれり！ 記念に　あげる。
Remember how you praised me
for the wonderful job I did?
フン！　下衆め。
I'm the one who disabled him!
二度と　ふざけたまねができぬよう 左手も　そぎ落としてくれる！
But I'm the one who held him in place—
あっ！
Enough.
さっきから言ってるだろ？ 「あげる」って。
Make yourself scarce.
望み通りにしてやる！
F-For...
おっと！　カストロ選手の片方が 猛然と突進！ うあ！
Forgive me!
あ！　なんとヒソカ選手 残った左腕も　自ら献上！
Was that story true?
何を考えているんだ　この人は！
Wh-Why, if it isn't Bihorn-sama...
何!?
Yes, there really was a rare human. Not that!
やはり　「ダブル」のほうで 攻撃して来たか。 もし　本体で攻撃して来たら
Did you really take a bite? No, I took a bite of the normal
human, not of the rare—
カウンターを くれてやろうと思ったのに…。
It doesn't matter if it was rare or not.
こっちで。
Consuming the Queen's food
えっ!? あれ!?　切られたはずの 右腕が　元に戻っている！
is not permitted.
ウフフ…　これも手品です。 さて　どんな仕掛けでしょう？
I'll never do it again, so please spare me just this once, Bihorn-sama!
ウソだ… こんな芸当が可能なのは
Hold it! Come back here! Bihorn.
「念」を使っているからだ
Have you ever seen a rare human?
しかし　一体 どんな念能力を…
No, I've only heard about them from Zazan.
ウフフ…　どうした？ 怖いのかな？
Zazan, could you provide more detail
about this rare human? Sure.
タネが分からないから驚く 手品の基本だ。
Arrows of light...
君の「ダブル」をつくる力は 素晴らしい。 だが　もうネタは分かった。
I understand. That explains the hole in the skull of that grunt.
そこから　どんな攻撃が来るかも おおかた想像がつく。
Yes, that must be it.
それに対処する方法もね。
One mystery has been solved.
非常に残念だ。 君は　才能に溢れた使い手になる。
While the arrows are invisible to foot soldiers, an officer like Pike can see them. See them and stop them.
そう思ったからこそ 生かしておいたのに。
In other words, officers can capture them.
予知しよう　君は踊り狂って死ぬ。 クッ…。
Yes, like I did. That one was clearly different from
the other humans we've captured.
黙れ!!
Its whole body appeared to
be shining with life energy.
うっ！
That's how I knew
な…　なぜ　こっちを!? 「ダブル」ってのは
that it would have the nutritional
value of over a thousand humans.
通常の自分を イメージで再現するものだから
More than ten days' worth in one human?
キレイなんだよね。
If that's true, we're saved.
戦いの最中に出来た汚れまでは 再現しきれない。
It'd be far easier than carrying
ハッ…。 なんだ
a hundred humans around each day.
そんなことも知らなかったのか？
If we find one on the first day,
we can rest the next nine.
うぅ…。
Fool! They're rare because they're hard to find!
うっ…。
What? Again?
うわ!!
Understood. Is something wrong?
あぁ…！ 一体　目の前で 何が起こっているのか!?
Rammot is acting without my permission again.
何!?　一体どうやって攻撃を…
Damn! Why am I stuck eating horses?
いや　そんな場合じゃ　ない！ 「ダブル」を使ってトランプを…
Damn... This is all Colt's fault.
「念」によって　「ダブル」を つくり出すには 高い集中力が必要。
I want to eat humans!
君が　いくら自由に出したり 消したりができるといっても それは　正常な状態だからこそ。
First, I have to deal with Rammot. Otherwise, it sets a bad example.
どのくらい大変かというと その力を覚えてしまうと
What is this presence?
逆に他の力を 使えなくなってしまうほど。
Could it be?
カストロ選手　立てません！
Say...
ヒソカ選手のＫＯ勝ちです！
Something smells. Coming from over there.
ん？ あんた　バカでしょ。
It's like a morning sacrifice.
ウフ　そうかもね。
A ritual practiced by birds
called bull-headed shrikes.
わざわざ こんな　むちゃな戦い方してさ。
They impale their prey on sharp
objects, such as branches.
あれって何？ パフォーマンスのつもりなの？
Hey!
お…。
Trash.
はい　終わり。
Those are mine!
僕は　わざとケガをするのかも。
This guy is strong.
いいから　左手２０００万 右手５０００万　払いな。
Fighting him won't be easy.
あっそ。 残ってる傷痕は 自分で処置してね。
Gon... Killua...
サービス悪いねぇ。 あんたの「バンジーガム」と 「ドッキリテクスチャー」使えば
You two must deal with him yourselves.
ああ… 隠しといたほうが　いいかな？
That is a Chimera Ant soldier.
そのほうが　戦闘中に 自力で元に戻したっぽいもんね。
We will encounter many more like him.
タネも仕掛けもない ただのスカーフ。
I won't be able to help you during combat. If you can't defeat it, you'll have to leave.
「バンジーガム」で腕に貼り付け
You'll just be in my way.
腕が治ったように 見えるだろうね
Weren't you listening, Kite?
次は　左。
We are also pros!
よく伸び　素早く縮み 至る所に貼り付けることができ
Don't treat us like kids!
好きな時に　剥がすことができる
What trick is this?
ちなみに 「バンジーガム」って名前は
Suddenly, they feel far stronger.
ヒソカには そこがまた　楽しいんだろうね
Time to test it!
昔　大流行した いたずらシール入りの菓子が
Thunderbolt!
でも　この２つの能力を使った 僕の戦い さすがだったと思わない？
First comes rock...
はぁ？
Rock...
君には全部　見えてたんだろ？
Paper...
まぁ　そうだけど…。
Rock!
あの時　あんたは １３枚のトランプをまいて 気をそらし
Yes! Just enough!
さらには　１３枚のトランプも 床に貼り付けられていて
Bastards!
そこから伸びたオーラの先端は あんたの左手に握られていた。
I'm gonna eat you!
そして　スペードのエースを カストロに投げる際…。
I will! Remember this!
左手に握られた オーラを　同時に放ち
Our attacks...
付着。
They didn't work.
トランプから伸びている １３本のオーラと カストロをつなぎ合わせた。
That guy's smart.
しかし　カストロは そのことに気づかない。
He let his soldier do the fighting,
so he could learn our abilities.
「絶」を応用して　限りなくオーラを 見えにくい状態にしていたからね。
Are you coming?
でも　それには弱点がある。
There's no need to feel down.
Your attacks weren't that bad.
目にオーラを集中させ 注意深く見れば見破ることは可能。
If you wish to become stronger,
this is a perfect opportunity.
だけど　あんたは
But if you aren't prepared, you won't
be able to endure the ordeal.
異常と思える手品で カストロの注意をそらし さらに　自分が本気を 出していないことをアピールし
Whether we win or lose, hell lies ahead of us.
悪魔の周到さで
We're coming.
準備が　うまく行っていることを 確認した　あんたは
Yeah.
全ての準備が完了。
That hurts...
床に落ちたスカーフは
Damn...
すでに　「ドッキリテクスチャー」で 肌の質感が再現されている。 そして　カストロに 左腕を攻撃された瞬間
Don't lay a finger on them.
天井の右腕と　床のスカーフの 「バンジーガム」が発動。
I'm gonna get my revenge.
右腕が戻り　その傷口を スカーフが覆い隠し
I'll kill them... I'll eat them all!
右腕が復活したかのように見せる。
I'm willing to let you kill them.
でも　このパフォーマンスは 逆に
But you may not eat them.
カストロを 少し冷静にさせてしまったね。 実際に　ちぎれた腕が 元通りになるという
Bodies brimming with so much life
energy provide the finest nutrition.
あまりに不可思議な現象。
They must be fed to the Queen.
それが　手品の範疇を超えて 「念」によるものだということを
No way! Killing them won't be enough!
カストロに 気づかせてしまったからね。
I have to tear them to shreds,
fill my belly with them...
でも　あんたは　その微妙な カストロの心理変化を見逃さなかった。
Crap on their skulls, and crush them!
((君の「ダブル」をつくる力は 素晴らしい)) )
And even still... That still may not be enough to quell my fury!
((そこから　どんな攻撃が来るかも おおかた想像がつく))
I won't be satisfied with just killing them! Don't get above yourself.
)
This is an order.
You would defy your leader's command?
((君は　才能に溢れた 使い手になる))
It isn't just Yunju's team.
((そう思ったからこそ 生かしておいたのに))
The other teams do it all the time.
落ち着きかけた カストロの精神を…。
Cheetu and Hagya's teams
do whatever they want.
((予知しよう 君は踊り狂って死ぬ))
Their leaders enjoy the hunt! Is that true? Yeah!
再び揺さぶった。
They chase humans, kill them, then leave the dead bodies there.
) )
None of the other squadrons just haul
bodies back like industrious little drones, my dear leader Colt.
) 頼みの「ダブル」さえも
I'll transfer to a different squad if
that's what it takes to kill them.
簡単に弱点を 見つけられてしまった。 それでも冷静に戦えば 善戦くらいは　できたんだけどね。
Damn, it hurts!
けど… カストロは 精神的に追い詰められて…。
A reason? Because it's fun, of course. It's good that humans know how to speak.
)
That way, we know what
they think as they die.
結果　倒れた。
Once you've tried it, you can never go back.
自分に　最も適してるって 確信してんだろ？ カストロの 「ダブル」なんかと違って
Do you feel the same way, Cheetu?
敵に能力が知られても
You're wrong about one thing...
全くマイナスにならない 応用力があるからね。
Hagya's and my teams are meeting our quota.
じゃあ　私は戻るわ。
We use our free time to enjoy the hunt. However...
もうかい？ 仕事　終わったんだから 当然でしょ。
You shouldn't waste the Queen's
precious food for sport.
念糸の強度にも 限界があるんだから
Precious food? Don't make me laugh.
腕の組織が 全部　完全にくっつくまで 無理しちゃダメよ。
There are more of them than she'll ever need.
あっ　そうだ　肝心の用事。 ん？
They're trash! I'm just taking out the trash.
メッセージの変更よ ８月３０日　正午までに
Got a problem with that? Not at all!
「暇な奴」改め　「全団員必ず」 ヨークシンシティに集合。
Do you know about the rare humans? Rare humans?
団長も来るのかい？
Oh...
恐らくね。
The ones that are overflowing with life energy?
今までで　一番大きな 仕事になるんじゃない？
I haven't seen one yet.
今度すっぽかしたら 団長自ら　制裁に乗り出すかもよ。 それは怖い。
If you do, capture it alive and bring it back.
残念。
Fine.
キルア！ ヒソカの試合　どうだった？
I'll take that as a promise.
勝ったのは　ヒソカ？
Fool. You think I'd keep that promise?
さっきのはウソだ。 えっ？
Let's find a rare one and eat it. Let's eat!
キルアでも分からないなんて…。
How's Rammot doing?
ゴン。
Tonight will be critical.
俺達も　もっと「念」の能力を 上げないとな。
But his anger and stamina
should see him through it.
うん！
Still, our army seems to have
too much personality.
あいつは語らない
Are you counting the humans you capture?
過去に あんまり興味がないんだ
Perhaps we should have everyone
assemble to discuss this.
多分　明日には カストロの顔さえ忘れてる
No, we operate at different times now. Assembling everyone is impossible.
あいつは属さない
I'll talk to each leader and devise a solution.
あいつは　自分以外の 誰にも属さない
What about the Queen? She's busy nourishing the King.
自分が最強だと 思っているから
We can't distract her.
クモか…。
This is ugly...
そろそろ狩るか。
So this is the hidden side of NGL.
彼にとっては　「幻影旅団」すらも 狩りの対象でしかなかった
The silence of the drug factory
overtaken by the Chimera Ants